# Bryce J. Tham Undergraduate, Computer Science

## SUMMARY

I am a fourth-year Computer Science major specializing in information and algorithms. I have worked primarily in Python and Java, but also some C/C++. I also have experience in database design and web development. I am interested in software engineering, human-computer interaction, and data informatics.

#### **EDUCATION**

B.S. in Computer Science, Class of 2017
 Donald Bren School of ICS, UC Irvine
 Specialization (Double): Information & Algorithms
 ICS Honors Program Student, UROP Fellow, 3.992 GPA

### **SKILLS** (by order of strength)

- Programming: Python, Java, C/C++
- Database Design: SQL/MySQL, Informatica
- Web Development: HTML, CSS, PHP, JavaScript

#### **EXPERIENCE**

AR Applications Research Assistant | UCI Institute for Software Research

April 2016 - Present

- Work with Dr. Walt Scacchi on an IoT-based augmented reality project for smart workers in advanced manufacturing.
- Research training techniques and interactive game-based systems to illustrate conceptual augmented learning.
- Write design documents, attributed directed graph models, and problem specifications for the manufacturing simulation.
- Create a prototype illustrating the conceptual implications of augmented reality in the context of real manufacturing settings.
- Data Warehouse Developer Intern | UCI Office of Information Technology

April 2015 - Preser

- Compare and write reports for hundreds of tables during the company's database migration away from Talend.
- Develop dozens of Informatica ETL mappings and sessions as part of the legacy ODS conversion.
- Update the Data Warehouse website with new content, including resolving security issues caused by SQL injection.
- Technology Chair | Circle K International

April 2015 - March 2016

- Managed content and resources for members including general information, weekly updates, calendar events, and media.
- Developed new features and tools for the website such as a personal events portal and a smart announcements system.
- Managed a group of 4 students in organizing the club's first Technology Internship Program.
- Received the Distinguished Appointed Board Officer award for demonstrating excellent achievement in service.
- Lab Tutor | Donald Bren School of ICS

September 2014 – March 2015

- Tutored over 50 students in various ICS courses including Programing With Software Libraries and Intermediate Programming.
- Wrote pedagogical materials as resources for future students and proctored/facilitated in-lab examinations.

#### **PROJECTS**

Bubble Buddy (Lead Designer, Programmer)

April 2016

Bubble Buddy is a web-based virtual communication companion designed for young children with autism who struggle with communication, identifying emotions, and learning by interacting with them using typical everyday conversation.

Completed for: Autism App Jam 2016; Programmed in: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, MEAN stack; Awards/Honors: Winner (2nd Place), Hype Award

Fabflix (Programmer)

January 2016 - March 2016

Fabflix is a web-based interface that allows customers to browse/search for movie information, add interesting movies to their shopping cart, and check out.

Completed for: Project In Databases And Web Applications; Programmed in: Java, HTML, CSS, MySQL, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap

UC Irvine Circle K Website (Technology Chair, Content Manager, Programmer)

April 2015 - March 2016

The UC Irvine Circle K Website utilizes key web development techniques and open-source software solutions to create a reliable and robust website as a resource hub for members and a means of organizing club secretarial information.

Completed for: Circle K International: Programmed in: HTML, CSS, MySQL, JayaScript, iQuery, PHP, Bootstrap: Awards/Honors: Outstanding Club

Completed for: Circle K International; Programmed in: HTML, CSS, MySQL, JavaScript, jQuery, PHP, Bootstrap; Awards/Honors: Outstanding Club Website (1st Place)

MedLight (Programmer, UI Designer)

November 2014

MedLight is a mobile application that uses a newsfeed-style of updating system in order to streamline information and communication between healthcare providers and their patients to keep all relevant personnel updated on the patient's health. Completed for: Med AppJam 2014; Programmed in: Swift, Xcode